Aum.
The neon glows, the river deep
Promises this town can't keep Another city,
another sign This ain't your journey, it's not
mine
They're singing songs of love and truth In every
smoky, crowded booth I see the dream, I see the
fame But all I feel is burning shame Oh
Nashville, what am I doing here Drowning in a sea
of unspoken fear Every mile's a chain, every
town's a cell Trapped inside this four-day hell
I wish that I I could turn this bus around But I'm
westward broken and silence is the only sound
She's staring out the window pane At her own
world of sunnin' and rain She doesn't see I'm
miles away Or hear the words I'll never say
Just a body in the sea
Headin' down a dead end street A piece of luggage
that she brings With broken hopes and broken
wings
Oh, Nashville, what am I doing here? Drowning in
a sea of unspoken fear Every mile's a chain,
every town's a cell Trapped inside this
four-day hell I wish that I I could turn this bus
around But I'm westward broken and silence is
the only sound
Oh
Oh, Nashville, what am I doing here? Drowning in
a sea of unspoken fear. Every mile's a chain,
every town's a cell. Trapped inside this
four-day hell, I wish that I I could turn this bus
around But I'm westward broken and silence is
the only sound